Elif Kaner

3D Animator

New York, NY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Elif-Kaner/7bfeaec6783d5146

I am a recent graduate from Drexel University's Animation and Visual Effects program with a minor in Video Production. I have a passion for character animation and love to animate in both realistic and cartoony styles. I just finished a 10 month production of my senior project, Broken Pieces, where I worked as the Producer, Animation Director, and Lead Animator. I also love stop motion animation and would be interested in working on a stop motion animation project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Producer, Animation Director, Lead Animator

Screaming Goat Animation Studios - Philadelphia, PA - March 2016 to June 2017

- Directed animation team to ensure consistency and high quality performance for 90 shot animation
- · Managed production team of 6 differing roles to guarantee efficiency and professional polish
- Animated 50 out of 90 shots of 6-minute short film
- Created and modified facial rigs for 4 separate characters
- · Strengthened pre-visualization workflow by implementing self captured and cleaned motion capture
- Conceptualized and developed 9 sets of clothing for 6 characters using Marvelous Designer

Motion Graphic Designer

Visual Innovations - Philadelphia, PA - March 2016 to September 2016

- Customized creative toolkits for clients while communicating specific brand identity
- Developed animated logos for Visual Innovations and clients
- Organized structural framework and revitalized design of company's website

Animator

Drexel University - Philadelphia, PA - June 2015 to June 2016

Independent Project - Sean Connery Face Animation

- Worked with client from high-end Center City restaurant on unique face animation
- · Motion captured facial animation using Faceware Analyzer and applied the data to models
- Animated models using Faceware Retargeter to reflect reverse aging process

3D Apprentice

1000 Volt Post Production - Istanbul - June 2014 to August 2014

- Strengthened animation skills by working with animation director, particularly on walk cycles in Maya
- Created short animations for commercial advertising clients
- Built test versions of 3D models for telephone and cable advertisements using Maya

Assistant Teacher

Amity School Karate Program - Brooklyn, NY - September 2011 to September 2013

- Coached and trained karate students for ages 4-12
- Led team of 25 karate students to organize training hall everyday, both before and after training
- Assisted coach to arrange and organize activities and belt tests

EDUCATION

BS in Animation and Visual Effects with a minor in Video Production

Drexel University - Philadelphia, PA September 2013 to June 2017

SKILLS

Animation (4 years), Autodesk Maya (4 years), Adobe Creative Suite (4 years), Autodesk MotionBuilder (3 years), Nuke (3 years), Faceware (2 years), Vicon Blade (3 years), Marvelous Designer (1 year), HTML 5 (3 years), CSS3 (3 years), Motion Capture (3 years)

LINKS

http://www.elifkaner.com